aeseducation.com 2017-07-14

# Privacy Policy for Applied Educational Systems, Inc.

## What Information is Collected?

AES collects basic personal information for users who have registered for our site. At sign-up for teachers, we collect name, login credentials, email address and school name. During enrollment at the direction of a teacher or administrator, students registering in one of their teachers’ courses and we collect student names and login credentials to allow teachers to monitor student progress and collect grades. We do not collect any student information beyond what is needed for the teacher to identify the student’s account.

## Analytics / Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, or to improve marketing, analytics, or website functionality.

## Tracking Technology (Cookies)

And like many other websites, we may use cookies. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer.

## How We Use Collected Information?

Any personal information will never be sold or rented to third parties

We use teacher information to provide information and service to users. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, new products and services, special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website's terms and conditions. Users can opt out of further email communication.

We do not use student information in any way to contact them, share information with third parties or build student profiles. We use the student information provided for the specific, limited educational purpose and intent stated in this agreement. Any other use is prohibited.

Student information access is limited to only those employees who have a legitimate educational need to access the information and are required to keep the information confidential.

## Legal Compliance

We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability.

## How is Information Stored and Protected?

Web traffic is protected with HTTPS TLS 1.2 services with an (enhanced verification) Symantec Class 3 EV Certificate. Media traffic is protected by a standard certificate. All traffic is redirected to https by default.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personal information submitted, both during transmission and once received. In the event of a breach of personal information we will alert the educational institution and users within 24 hours of confirmation of breach.

We will not keep personal information longer than the time frame necessary to support the purpose of the contract or as authorized by the parent/student. At any time an educational institution, parent or authorized person wishes to delete personal information, they may do so by contacting us at support@aeseducation.com.

## Policy Changes

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If material changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us at support@aeseducation.com.

## Questions or Concerns

Any questions or concerns about this website privacy policy should be brought to our attention by sending an email to support@aeseducation.com and providing us with information relating to your concern.

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:

Applied Educational Systems, Inc.  
208 Bucky Drive  
Lititz, PA 17543   USA

## California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an email to support@aeseducation.com or write us at the following address:

Applied Educational Systems, Inc.  
208 Bucky Drive  
Lititz, PA 17543    USA
